[Music]
foreign
fonts are like a big pot of money that's
managed by experts who decide where to
invest it in like stocks in one you can
also buy and sell shares in the fund
easily meanwhile insurance policies are
like safety nets you buy it for benefits
that can cover future financial needs
like a health emergency
some insurance policies have an
investment component however these
products are not really designed for
investing so which one is right for you
it depends on what you want to do with
your money if you want to grow your
money and have control over your
Investments T12 funds are ideal or if
you want to protect yourself from
unexpected costs insurance policies are
the way to go or better yet go for both
the good news is you can seek advice
from professionals they can help you
figure out what's best for your needs
and guide you along the way
so ready to invest just go back to our
email and click invest now or go to
sunlightfont.com click buy now and start
investing today but if you want to know
more join Sun life's mf101 webinar and
be on your way to a brighter future
[Music]